A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial, Bob Wands, Series 5 FA458
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial, 1958-1974; 5
  - Contact Sheets, 1959-1964
    - Contact Sheets, 1963 January-December; D5000-D5056
      - Nigerian Ambassador His Excellency Julius M. Udochi presents ebony carving to Nelson A. Rockefeller. Also Consul General LSM Osabase, Commercial Vice Chairman & Henry Wheatley, director of NYS. International Official Visitors Office (55th St.), 1963 December 12; D5056 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Contact Sheets, 1964 January-December; D6000-6032
      - Press Conference-Announcement of telegram to Sen. Goldwater congratulating him on candidacy for Republican nomination (55th St.), 1964 January 3; D6000 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Opening of Legislature - Nelson A. Rockefeller speech (Albany), 1964 January 8; D6001 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - President of Italy, Segni, Nelson A. Rockefeller (Waldorf), 1964 January 17; D6002 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - California Trip (San Francisco, L.A.), 1964 Janaury 28-30; D6003 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Swear Ins - Mario Biaggi & F. William Guma by Secretary of State John Lomenzo (270 Broadway), 1964 January 30; D6004 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Real Estate Advisory Comm. with Lomenzo (270 Broadway), 1964 January 30; D6005 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Swear Ins - meetings (cemetery board) & Secretary of State, John Lomenzo (270 Broadway), 1964 January 31; D6006 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Regional Directors meeting of Republican State Committees (521 Fifth), 1964 February 1; D6007 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Opening of "Rockefeller for President" HQ (521 Fifth), 1964 February 5; D6008 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Washington, DC - Oregon trip (Washington/Portland Medford/Roseburg/Salem), 1964 February 6-8; D6009 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Mrs. Rockefeller meets campaign workers (521 Fifth), 1964 February 14; D6010 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - New Hampshire trip (New Hampshire), 1964 February 19-22; D6011 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Young Republicans from all states meeting (521 Fifth), 1964 February 22; D6012 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller looks at answers from questionnaires (55th St.), 1964 February 26; D6014A (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - New Hampshire Trip 2 (New Hampshire), 1964 March 4-8; D6014 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - New Hampshire Election Night (521 Fifth), 1964 March 10; D6015 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - California Trip (California), 1964 March 11-14; D6016 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Oregon Trip (Oregon), 1964 March 30-31; D6017A (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - California Trip (California), 1964 April 1-2; D6017 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Detroit Trip (Detroit), 1964 April 6; D6018 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Baltimore & Washington, DC (MD, Washington DC), 1964 April 8-9; D6019 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Rockefeller Center (plaque & building) (Rockefeller Center), 1964 April 14-16; D6020 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Oregon (4/17), Palm Springs (4/18-9) S. California (4/20), New Orleans (4/21) (West Coast/ Louisiana), 1964 April 17-21; D6021 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Eisenhower with Nelson A. Rockefeller at Palm Springs (Palm Springs), 1964 April 19; D6022 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - World's Fair Opening Day (World's Fairgrounds), 1964 April 22; D6023 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - World's Fair New York Day (World's Fairgrounds), 1964 April 23; D6024 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Oregon (4/27-28) California (4/29) West Virginia (4/30-5/1) (West Coast/ W. Virginia), 1964 April 27-May 1; D6026 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - California Testimonial Pix Oregon - final campaigning Northern California, Oregon (S. & N. Calif., Oregon), 1964 May 6-15; D6027 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller at Headquarters - with press (521 Fifth), 1964 May 16; D6028 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Meeting with Romney at W.F. (World's Fair), 1964 May 18; D6029 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - California Campaigning (California), 1964 May 19; D6030 (Box 12, Folder 21-22)
      - Election night (521 Fifth), 1964 June 2; D6030A (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - California Press Conference (521 Fifth), 1964 June 3; D6030B (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - NY Republican State Com. (Ten Eyck - Albany), 1964 June 11; D6031 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Meeting - Chancellor Erhard (Waldorf Hotel), 1964 June 11; D6032 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - San Francisco and Cow Palace, 1964 July; S.F. (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Negatives
    Conditions Governing Access
    Negatives are restricted from scholarly access. For RAC staff only.
    Arrangement
    Negatives are arranged chronologically by alphanumeric number (Boxes 13-17) or otherwise by number (boxes 18-19).
    - D100, D101, D104, D105 - D125, D127 - D214 (Box 13)
    - D2000 - D2007 (Box 13)
    - D2009 - D2017 (Box 13)
    - D2021, D2023, D2024 (Box 13)
    - D2026 - D2031, D2033 (Box 13)
    - D2035 - D2053 (Box 13)
    - D2055 - D2064 (Box 13)
    - D2065 - D2126 (Box 14)
    - D3000 - D3055 (Box 14)
    - D3500 - D3527 (Box 14)
    - D4004 - D4051, D4053 (Box 15)
    - D4055 - D4060 (Box 15)
    - D6003 - D6021 (Box 16)
    - D6022 - D6033 (Box 17)
    - 0406 - 0830 (Box 18)
    - 0902 - 11021 (Box 19)
  - Other Prints, Negatives, etc., 1958-1974
    - New York State Republican Convention, 1958 (Box 20)
    - Gubernatorial Campaign, 1958 (Box 20)
    - Gubernatorial Campaign, 1962 (Box 20)
    - Presidential Campaign, 1964 (Box 20)
    - Presidential Campaign, 1968 (Box 20)
    - Gubernatorial Campaign, 1970 (Box 20)
    - Presidential Campaign, 1972 (Box 20)
    - Inauguration, 1958 (Box 21)
    - Ceremonies, 1959-1973; 3 folders (Box 21)
    - Ceremonies, undated (Box 21)
    - New York World's Fair, 1964 (Box 21)
    - Legislators, 1963 (Box 21)
    - "Meet the Press", 1973 (Box 21)
    - Critical Choices Dinner, 1973 December 3 (Box 21)
    - American College of Cardiology Annual Meeting, 1974 (Box 21)
    - VP Years (Box 21)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mary Todhunter Clark Rockefeller and Children (Box 22)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Margaretta Fitler Murphy Rockefeller and Children (Box 22)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller and Dwight David Eisenhower (Box 22)
    - R. McManus (Box 22)
    - Photos Gathered by R. McManus (Box 22)
    - NY State Executive Mansion & Occupants (Historic Photos and Notes) (Box 22)
    - NY State Executive Mansion - Fire, 1961 (Box 22)
    - NY State Executive Mansion - Interior Views, Exterior Views, and Decorations (Box 22)
    - Republican Convention, 1960 (Box 23)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Associates (Box 23)
    - Martin Luther King Jr. (Box 23)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Various Personalities (Box 23)
    - Ceremonies, 1959-1973 (Box 24)
    - Presidential Campaign, 1964; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Presidential Campaign, 1968 (Box 24)
    - Photo Albums (Box 25)
      - Thruway Tourist Information Center - Dedication, 1961 September 14
      - KXJB and KXGO TV Stations - North Dakota, 1960 June
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portraits (Box 26)
    - Presidential Campaign, 1964 (Box 27)
    - Slides and Negatives, 1968 and 1970 (Box 28)
    - Slides and Negatives (Box 29)
    - Unidentified Print (Box 30)
    - Unidentified Contact Prints, 3 Folders (Box 31)
    - Bob Wands' Bills, 1972 (Box 31)
    - Miscellany (Box 32)
      - Plate - Binghamton Sun Bulletin, 1976 September 17
      - Die - Republican Governors' Association Conference, 1973 May 9-12
      - "Numbers to Remember" - Photo Department, 1970-1971